<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Victor Mendonça</title>
    <link>https://geekit.ca/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Victor Mendonça</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Victor Mendonça</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://geekit.ca/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://geekit.ca/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekit.ca/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Biography Victor is an independent IT contractor with strong Linux background living in Toronto.
His company, GeekIT Consulting Inc., specializes in Linux, and for many years, in the design and deployment of Manhattan’s WMOS (Warehouse Management Open Systems), a supply chain software stack solution by Manhattan Associates. Some of his clients are well known names in the Canadian industry, like LCBO, Shoppers Drug Mart, Home Hardware, and Fujitsu Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Experience</title>
      <link>https://geekit.ca/home/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekit.ca/home/experience/</guid>
      <description>Download my Resume here.
Linux Administrator Fujitsu Americas, Toronto, ON - Dec 2020 - Present
 Supported a cluster of 40 WildFly servers (on RHEL 7) running on Azure infrastructure with Active MQ as the message broker and Azure SQL Database as backend Drastically improved time spent on operational tasks (support, investigation and other day-to-day activities) by automating them with Bash and PowerShell scripts Introduced Ansible for automation of OS patching and configuration management improving outage time Developed a Docker environment used to test Ansible deployments with Molecule Fixed WildFly startup issues related to deprecated configuration provided by the vendor, allowing fully automation of nightly shutdown of environments that saved the company thousands of dollars Improved application startup by adding multiple stage checks to the startup scripts Automated the setup of a local Linux environment (WSL) used by other infrastructure team members saving time spent on manual work Supported and applied code changes/fixes to multiple Azure pipelines used for automating database refreshes and Java deployment to all environments Configured and Maintained Grafana dashboards (including alerts) using Azure Application Insights and Logs as data source Improved and authored multiple knowledge base articles on Azure DevOps Wiki  WMOS Manhattan Support (Consultant) LCBO, Toronto, ON - Aug 2019 - Mar 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://geekit.ca/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekit.ca/home/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://geekit.ca/home/publications_selected/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekit.ca/home/publications_selected/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://geekit.ca/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekit.ca/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>