<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Victor Mendonça</title>
    <link>https://geekit.ca/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Victor Mendonça</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Victor Mendonça</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://geekit.ca/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://geekit.ca/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekit.ca/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Biography Linux Systems Administrator with 15+ years of experience managing and optimizing RHEL and other Linux environments in enterprise settings. Skilled in automation with Ansible and Red Hat Satellite, middleware support (JBoss/WildFly), and monitoring with Grafana, Splunk, and Azure Monitor. Recognized for exceptional attention to detail, producing clear documentation and runbooks that improve consistency and onboarding. Experienced in hybrid infrastructures with Azure and AWS, with a strong passion for automation and process improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Experience</title>
      <link>https://geekit.ca/home/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekit.ca/home/experience/</guid>
      <description>Download my Resume here.
Linux Administrator (Consultant) Wawanesa Insurance, Toronto, ON - Jan 2024 - Apr 2025
 Managed on-prem and cloud Linux servers consisting of RHEL and Amazon Linux Responsible for Linux OS patching, support and configuration Created documentation for various day-to-day activity improving team consistency when executing tasks Automated Satellite content view publish/promotion/clean up, and maintenance via Ansible playbooks, decreasing the time spent on activities and minimizing the chance for human error Automated ServiceNow changes and requests creation with Ansible, as well as new incident handling and closing  Linux Administrator Fujitsu Americas, Toronto, ON - Dec 2020 - Dec 2023</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://geekit.ca/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekit.ca/home/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://geekit.ca/home/publications_selected/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekit.ca/home/publications_selected/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://geekit.ca/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekit.ca/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>